downloadfreely.com 2015-12-18

# Privacy Policy - Download Freely

**DOWNLOAD FREELY PRIVACY STATEMENT**

ATTENTION ALL USERS OF WEBSITES OWNED AND OPERATED BY DOWNLOAD FREELY, LLC:

This Privacy Statement explains how Download Freely, LLC, a limited liability company under the laws of the State of Delaware, U.S.A. ("Download Freely" "we," or "us"), collects and uses the information concerning users ("Users" or "you") of its downloadfreely.com and openfreely.com websites (the "Websites").

This policy applies to the Websites only. Download Freely owns, manages, and is responsible for all pages of the Websites. Users with privacy questions should send an email to contract@downloadfreely.com.

YOU AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT WHEN YOU USE THE WEBSITE. IF YOU DON'T AGREE WITH THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT, DON'T USE THE WEBSITE. WE MAY REVISE THIS POLICY AT ANY TIME. WE WILL ONLY NOTIFY USERS VIA THE WEBSITE IF THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT IS CHANGED. CHECK THE WEBSITE FREQUENTLY FOR CHANGES. CHANGES WILL BE EFFECTIVE WHEN POSTED. USE OF THE WEBSITE AFTER CHANGES HAVE BEEN POSTED WILL BE CONSIDERED TO BE THE ACCEPTANCE AND AGREEMENT TO THE CHANGES.

**The Information and Content Covered by this Privacy Statement**  
This Privacy Statement applies to all information we collect on the Websites and all information you may provide to us via the Websites. The Websites may include message areas that allow the posting or submission of information to us or the Websites. If a User posts information other Users may be able to view the information. Be careful when posting personal or personally identifiable information. Other users who can view the information may misuse it. We do not have any direct control over the use that other users may make of information you post to our Websites for public viewing.

**Data Collection**  
We may collect non-personal and non-identifiable information about use of the Websites from you and other users to evaluate the layout, design or effectiveness of the Websites. The data collected is used to make the Websites perform better. Improvements we may make include the upgrades or changes to the design of the Websites interface, graphics and layout changes, functionality improvements, and changes to marketing or advertising features. The Websites technology used to gather and analyze the non-personal and non-identifiable information includes IP addresses, browser cookies, browser detection methods, web log files, and web analytics software. 

**Special Offers**  
You may be invited to participate an optional or special promotion, poll, drawing, survey or offer, and we may ask you to provide personal information for this. We uses information collected through these methods to learn more about customers and improve our products and services. You may choose to opt-out.

**Cookies and Other Data Tools**  
The Internet location of computers are defined by IP addresses. The geographic location of Websites users may be learned from IP addresses. Cookies are data files placed onto the file storage of a computer to identify the computer when the User returns to the Websites. Cookies enable us to recognize your computer and deliver content especially for you. Users may modify their browser preferences to accept all cookies, be notified when a cookie is saved on their computer, or reject all cookies. Users should consult their browser documentation for help on with cookies. If you modify your cookie preferences, certain features of the Websites may not be available or work.

We use information about the type of web browser you are using to optimize the performance of the Websites and to discover which browsers are the most used. We examine web log files and use web analytics software to determine how users navigate through the Websites. We also may analyze how long users spend on portions of the Websites to the extent possible.

We may enter legal agreements with other third parties for services such as customer email handling, other communications, website analytics, and other services. 

**The Websites are Not Intended for Young Children**  
The Websites is not to be used or accessed by children under the age of 13 for any purpose.

**When Information Disclosure May Be Required**  
We reserve the right to disclose information as we deem required by law and also when we determine that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights. We may elect to sell all or substantially all of the assets or operations of our company to a third party, including the Websites. If this happens, information about Users may be among the assets that are transferred to the third party. 

**Issues Involving Other Websites**  
The Websites may include links to other websites. Also, we may make special offers to users downloading a software product from the Websites. The offer may be made by a third party contractor. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of our contractors. We encourage you to be aware when they leave our Websites and to read the privacy policies of all other websites you visit or submit any information to. Some websites we link to may be co-branded with our business name or trademarks. Other websites may have a look and feel similar to our Websites. The uniform resource locator (URL) shown by your browser may be the only way to determine that you are visiting a different website. 

This Privacy Statement applies only to the downloadfreely.com and openfreely.com websites owned and operated by Download Freely, LLC. All rights reserved.

THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT HAS IMPORTANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. PLEASE READ IT CAREFULLY AND FULLY.

Copyright © 2011-2012 Download Freely, LLC

_Last Updated: May 10, 2012_
